Rizky Faza

System Administrator

 $Pandan\ wangi\ District\ , Kencana\ Arum\ 4\ Q/11,\ Ciwastra\ ,\ Buah\ batu,\ 40286\ |\ 0896-3458-3164\ |\ rizkyfaza61@gmail.com$

netchill00.systems



Summary

Working hard, being responsible, and **being thorough** in doing work is the basis for being a professional with the skills that I have and developed during my 3 years experience at SMK. I prefer to see progress gradually during the process so that the results obtained still rely on **quality**.

Education

Vocational High School 4 Bandung

SMK Negeri 4 Bandung

Jurusan: Teknik Komputer dan Jaringan

Work experience

IT Support

PT Pindad Enjinering Indonesia

Responsibility:

- Maintaining Hardware and Software
- Installing and Maintaining Network Connection
- Troubleshooting Hardware
- Troubleshooting in Network Connection based on TCP/IP
- Configuring Network Tools

Intern System Administrator

October 2019 - December 2019

PT Exabytes Network Indonesia

Responsibility:

- Mounting and Setting new server in Data Center
- Maintainance server in Data Center
- Server and Network Uptime Monitoring with Nagios
- Helping Customer with their VPS, Hosting, Email Server
- Troubleshooting VPS, Hosting, Email Server

Intern Fiber Optic Support

PT Jabar Telematika (ISP)

Responsibility:

- Network and Server Monitoring
- Troubleshooting Fibre Optic Connection
- Installing new node in Home
- Managing Bandwidth Connection

October 2018 - December 2018

Skills

Windows Server

- Hyper V Management
- IIS Configuration
- DNS & FTP Server Configuration

TCP/IP

2016 - 2019

Feb 2020 - Now

- IP Subnetting (VLSM,CIDR)
- OSI 7 Layer
- Protocol Communication
- Network Topology

Troubleshooting

- Mail Server
- Web Server
- Hardware Maintenance
- Control Panel Server (cPanel + Plesk)

MikroTik

- Router Basic
- Hotspot Configuration
- Wireless Configuration
- Basic Routing
- CAPsMan Server and Client

Cisco

- Router Security
- Routing
- Router Management
- Switch VLAN Management

Linux Administration

• Installing, Maintainancing Server

- Based focused on CentOS & Debian
- Control Panel (Plesk + cPanel)
- Service Instalation
- VM Management(SolusVM)
- Backup + Restore Management

Trainings

• Training CCNA Routing and Switching (Netvlops Academy)

- Pelatihan Olimpiade MikroTik 2018 (LPKIA)
- Python: Hands-on Introduction for Beginners (online) task in Google Code-in
- GITS Class #15: Lara-vue (Laravel + Vue.js)

Certification

- CCNA RSITN
- LSP SKKNI Junior Network Administrator
- TOEIC

Created with 🔁 VisualCV

